No fair! Yor gets to have all the fun!
I wanted to go on a luxury
cruise vacation, too!
It's not a vacation.
She's entertaining guests for work.
Well, I could've done that, too!
Apparently, one of the guests had a baby,
so the requirement was whoever
went had to have a kid.
There's also the fact that
they're from the same place.
That's what the guy from HR told me.
I'm so jealous!
She's probably having an
elegant dinner right now!
Dang it! I bet it tastes amazing!
But having sausages and beers
right after work is pretty great, too.
Totally.
The Fearsome Luxury Cruise Ship
Isn't the food here great?
It's prepared by chefs who work at a five-star
hotel that's headquartered in Berlint.
Also, the company that made parts of this ship
and the company that handled the interior
design are all funded by our city.
Now, let's stop the unrefined chatter.
Truly, I'd love to eat
at that hotel someday.
This is delicious.
I'm so nervous, I can't taste a thing.
Calm down.
The enemy wouldn't try to attack
in such a crowded space.
And third-class passengers, such as your
family, can't enter this restaurant.
So concentrate on the job.
Y-Yes, sir.
Well, why don't we go have a few
more drinks downstairs, Mister Grey?
S-Sure...
I'm going to head back to the room.
Be cautious of anyone following
you on the way back to the room.
Understood.
There are no signs that anyone came in here.
Good.
I guess this day ended
with nothing happening.
W-We can't let our guard down, though!
There's no guarantee that
the enemy isn't on the ship.
We have thirty hours before we
rendezvous with the other ship.
If I were the enemy, I'd strike right
before you were going to move over.
I wouldn't want to cause a commotion on
a ship where I'd have no way to escape.
Even if intel hasn't been leaked,
there's always a chance the
enemy could strike somehow.
Tomorrow will probably
be our moment of truth.
Er, that's what the director said.
Let's keep our guard up!
You're right. I'm sorry.
Maybe I just want to relax and
believe there isn't an enemy.
But this isn't just my problem anymore.
I need to get a grip.
Right.
Once we get to our destination
and confirm that you're safe,
please play with him outside
as much as possible.
You really don't seem like someone
from the underworld.
Huh? Oh, I'm terribly sorry! I'll try harder.
Even if we're able to escape safely,
what are all of you going to do afterward?
If we can't sense any threat from the
enemy, we'll all be standing by.
We've told the two city hall workers
who don't know what's going on
that the Greys would like to be
by themselves on the third day,
so that won't be a problem.
The director will smooth things over
when you leave the ship, as well.
What about you? You're not
going to see your family?
Huh? No, I mean, I'm working... um...
I have told them that I would contact
them when I had a spare moment, but...
This ship is stopping at an island
resort on the third day, isn't it?
I hope you and your family can also
enjoy yourselves without interruption.
No, I, uh... Mm...
Mm, mm!
Don't eat too much just
because it's a buffet.
I played lots. Now I'm starving.
Could you not be so messy when you eat?
It's been a while since we've
had dinner without Mama.
Yeah, it's a bit lonely.
Papa is so lonesome.
I-I am not! I only said
something because you did!
Just eat so we can back to the room.
These cashew nuts are exquisite.
Well, we sure drank quite a bit, Mr. Grey.
Yeah, I definitely didn't.
That was an exciting game of darts!
You're so good, Mr. Grey.
Sorry, I forgot something.
Aw, you're so clumsy, Director!
We're gonna keep heading back.
There are plenty of things
to do besides darts.
Why don't we have another
drink, Mr. Grey? Come on!
No... I'll be heading back.
Tch.
Answer my questions with a yes or a no.
Are you an assassin hired
by Leonardo Hapoon?
You'll only get two seconds to answer.
Next, I'll break your leg.
Are you one of Hapoon's assassins?
Are there any assassins
other than yourself?
How many in total?
Oh, sorry about that. That wasn't
a yes or no question, was it?
Tell me how many friends you
have and their locations.
Th-They aren't my friends. And I have
no idea how many are on board.
We're all working on our own.
It's first come, first served.
There's some guy selling us intel.
That's what I was using to tail you guys.
Shaty Grey in room 8053...
Looks like I had the right person.
Oh, welcome back, Director.
What was that? You're about
to poop your pants, Mister Grey?
That's an emergency!
Let's hurry back to your room!
You two, rest up for tomorrow.
D-Director?
Several enemies have snuck on board.
They know your aliases and room.
Our organization was carrying
out this plan in utmost secrecy.
There's no way our intel
could've been leaked.
Do you have any ideas? Did you make
contact with someone outside?
No...
Did you?
No, I didn't, but, um...
Three days ago, I did make one phone call.
Just to my parents back home.
You fool!
I didn't say anything that would
jeopardize our plan. That's the truth!
Since I'll never see them again,
I just said my last goodbyes.
That's all it was! I swear!
Tch. Enough.
We don't have time to track the enemies.
"First come, first served"?
I was naïve...
They're not going to wait
until tomorrow to attack.
We probably won't be going out again tonight,
so why don't we take off our dresses?
You're right.
Director?
Oh, it's just room service.
I didn't order any.
You stole darts from the bar?
Don't shoot! There's a baby in here!
Wow...
We'll carry him into the room.
Try not to leave a blood trail.
G-Got it...
There are a lot of enemies on this ship?
Some intel's been leaked, too.
We're abandoning this room.
There are a number of rooms
open in second class.
You need to take these three
and head there immediately.
What are you going to do?
I'll meet up with you as
soon as I finish up here.
U-Understood.
There's a chance the ship might
turn back if there's a commotion.
If we're unable to hide the bodies,
please avoid fighting as much as you can.
Just in case, hide your
face with this mask. Hurry!
Hello, this is guest services.
Oh, hello. This is room 8053.
I'm very sorry. The mister and missus
had a rather violent argument,
and they broke the door... Yes.
We'd like to move to a different room.
I've lost contact with the Knocker.
The Shaty that was in room
8053 is definitely our target.
The passenger list also names a husband.
Including the woman's voice I heard,
there are at least three of them.
That's not counting the baby.
A bodyguard?
Looks like they're changing rooms.
Whatever room they move
to is probably a decoy.
Welp, looks like they're on their guard
because someone had to be impatient.
If their bodyguard is from Garden,
this isn't going to be easy.
Why don't we work together?
Which means no infighting, and we'll
just split the reward evenly.
We will share information at all times.
Sounds like a pain in the ass.
Wouldn't it be faster to kill any
woman with a baby we see on board?
Don't lump assassins in with murderers.
Our work is based on trust.
Many of the family's regular
patrons are aboard this ship.
If you want to get paid, then don't
cause any unnecessary commotion.
We'll also need you to keep reporting
to us without causing any leaks.
We're paying you good money.
I'm selling all of my information equally.
Do your best so no one gets ahead of you.
Hey... Won't these masks just
draw more attention to us?
It's all right.
There's a masquerade taking
place in Lounge No. 2.
Please do not remove them
under any circumstances.
And... I need the two of you to listen
to what I say without turning around.
We are probably being followed.
Ever since we left the room.
Hey, what are we going to do?!
Let's lose them before they
find out where we're going.
Th-This had better work...
They're heading to the stern.
Their destination is probably Lounge No. 2.
Okay, I'll make contact.
We're here!
Bloodlust.
They're coming! And in this huge crowd?!
If I intercept and kill them,
it'll cause a commotion.
Then the rendezvous may also be called off.
Hey.
Pardon.
Peacefully, without killing them...
Have they noticed me?
No, my location should still be safe.
I can take them down!
All I've gotta do is inject them
with this poison as I pass by.
I'll make sure it's quick—huh?!
Sir, you've had too much to drink.
And we're safe.
Huh? What is? Can I get my button back?
Wh-What the?! What just happened to him?!
Sir?
Hey, Andre! Our targets are
heading into the lounge!
Don't lose them! The black-haired
one must be their bodyguard!
Aim for the blonde from their blind spot!
Roger.
O-Oh, my.
Are you asking me to dance with you?
I'm terribly sorry. I'm not
very good at dancing.
And you know...
I may not look it, but I'm a married woman,
so I'll have to decline.
Have a wonderful night.
Andre, what happened?!
Please stay quiet for a while.
Come in! Hey, Andre!
It looks like we've lost them.
Let's hurry downstairs.
Once we go through the promenade,
we'll be in the second class area.
R-Right...
4th Deck
Shopping Promenade
Papa! I want this bony keychain!
You absolutely don't need it. Why would
they even sell those on this ship?
I want it! I want it! I want it! I want it!
I want it! I want it! I want it!
We're going back to our room. It's late.
Oddly enough...
There seem to be wiretaps
set in various places.
Countless members of the ruling
class and celebrities are aboard.
I'm sure there are plenty of
State Security Service members
who've snuck in to check on them.
Other than State Security Service members,
I've spotted some other
suspicious-looking characters.
I'm going to try to stay
quiet and avoid them.
I want it! I want it! I want it now, dang it!
I want it! I want it! I want it! I want it!
Trying to stay quiet...
He should just buy it for her.
How cute!
Not good! They're hearing
this conversation, too.
Normally, a parent would
buy their child that.
You're suspicious. You must be a spy.
You piece of trash. You're under arrest.
Which is it?! Would normal parents buy their
child something in this situation or not?!
I mean, she clearly doesn't need this!
I can't say this will help
in her education, either.
But the wrong choice could
ultimately mean death...
I guess I don't need it after all.
Now she feels a little bad
I'll take them out.
Don't cause a commotion?
Hell if I care.
That broad and her little
brat are worth 400,000 dalc.
There's no way I'm splitting that with you
fools who are just pretending to be assassins.
I'm Sickle-and-Chain Barnaby...
and I never let my prey get away.
Sickle-and-Chain Barnaby?!
Who's that?
Here they come.
From what I heard, the black-haired
woman is an experienced bodyguard.
I'll take her out first.
Mama!
That assassin is going to
try to battle Mama here.
Should I buy it or not?
I'm gonna sic this chained frog on you!
Kapow
I hate frogs!
What's going on here?!
Y-Yor! You're an assassin who hates frogs?!
Let's get a divorce. The Forgers are done.
Let's get rid of Anya, too!
Eek!
Wh-What should I do?!
I was wrong, Anya.
Let's buy these bones and go.
It'll be a precious memory of our cruise.
I am a normal father. A good father.
Who cares about that stupid thing?!
Don't come over here!
What?!
Mama is about to end up in a battle!
Come on. I'll buy you this,
so cheer up. Okay?
If Papa leaves this store, he'll see them!
Kaplow
Eek! A battle!
What's going on here?!
What?! Yor, you go around having battles?!
If he even hears someone go,
"Eek!" it's the end!
I'm the one who said we should go on
this boat, so I have to do something...
Wha... What even is that face?!
Is it sadness? Anger?!
What exactly is this emotion?!
Is she that hurt because I refused
to buy her these little bones?!
Is she at the age where
she's emotionally unstable?!
Wait, no. You've known this, Twilight.
No matter how hard she tries to hide it...
She has a tremendous
darkness within her heart!
She's been hurting this whole time!
Uh...
Well, little Anya's care and education
are part of Strix, as well.
Handler must've seen through all of this!
That's why she tasked me with this peace
initiative mission labeled as a family vacation!
I must see this through!
Papa is always off the mark.
Um, are you looking for
something in particular?
Lately, this T-shirt and jacket with
the ship's logo are bestsellers.
For fathers, we have this tie with whales on it.
We even have matching caps
for father and child!
We have a fitting room right over
there so you can try everything on!
Er... I don't think I need any of that.
I don't have time for that.
Right now, I need to make
sure she's mentally stable.
Papa, you just don't get it.
Huh?
Adventures exist so you can
experience other exciting things.
It's because you're filled with
excitement that you end up
wanting to buy that bony
thing or a wooden sword.
Papa, you're not excited at all.
If you're going to be like that,
you're gonna make Anya sad.
I think you should use your whole body
to tell me just how excited you are.
That's right.
I cannot believe that I, Twilight, the man
with a thousand faces, had forgotten...
The most important thing
is to become my role!
The role of a cheerful dad having fun!
Miss, I'd like to try on those clothes.
In fact, I'll just wear them out.
Oh, sure.
Papa, I think those mister squid
pants are also quite fun.
I'd like to try on all the clothes
you have in this establishment.
Oh, of course. Right this way.
I pray that you come out looking cool.
Leave it to me.
Let me know if you need a
different size in anything!
Okay. I'll keep Papa trapped
in there to buy time!
Now I've gotta do something about Mama!
Huh?!
Oh, no!
I forgot that Papa is a master of disguise!
He can change in an instant!
I don't get it.
No matter how you look at it,
these clothes don't match at all!
Is this going to work?
What actually expresses excitement?
Is there even a best answer here?!
Damn it, it's no use!
I need to figure out a more perfect form!
Huh? They're not battling?
Huh?
She actually evaded that...
And while protecting those two.
I didn't sense his bloodlust
up until the last second.
He's...
strong.
The bright crimson that
appears right before my eyes
Stretches approximately 40,000 kilometers
Our wounds that inch closer behind us
Make us wander even more
when we're already lost
The unseeable, scentless, unmistakable future
Stabbed me in the back!
So...
Let me stay by your side tonight
Just for tonight, I'm going to be serious
Come closer to me
Even the future we prayed for
Has a different path
My dear
Our malice for each other
Might just get to us
Or maybe not
Who Is This Mission For?